24hourwristbands.com 2010-12-04

# Privacy Policy - Wristbands | Buy Custom Rubber Bracelets and Silicone Wristbands

|   |  |    
---  
|  |   |  |    
---|---|---|---  
   
|  |   | 

## NETBRANDS PRIVACY POLICY

|    
---|---|---|---  
  
[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") respects the privacy of anyone who uses any of NetBrands’s Web sites and any [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") online applications (NetBrands Order Forms, NetBrands Fax Order Sheets) 

[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") gathers important information from our visitors and customers. We publish this Privacy Policy to communicate how we gather and use information about you, how we protect it, and how you can participate in its protection. 

[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") will, from time-to-time, e-mail members of our e-mail list with special promotions and offers. This will help you take advantage of savings on products that may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive promotional e-mails, you can send an e-mail to [help@24hourwristbands.com](mailto:help@24hourwristbands.com) and please type "REMOVE FROM MAILING LIST" in the subject line of your e-mail. Removals are usually done within 24 hours. However, to ensure that the unsubscribe process has been completed successfully, please allow two weeks. 

[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") provides its service to you subject to the [NetBrands Terms of Service](http://24hourwristbands.com/terms-and-condition/ "Terms and Condition") and this Privacy Policy, which shall be deemed part of the [Terms of Service](http://24hourwristbands.com/terms-and-condition/ "Terms and Condition"). We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy. If we change it, we will provide notification of the change at least thirty (30) business days before the change takes effect and include directions for how you can respond to the change.   

|  |   | 

## COLLECTED INFORMATION

|    
---|---|---|---  
  
We require people who register to use a [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") online applications (the "Services") to give us contact information. Depending on the services chosen, we ask for contact and account information, such as name, company name, address, phone number, e-mail address, password and the number of users in the organization who will be using the Services, in addition to financial and billing information, such as billing name, address and credit card number. When you express interest in additional information, when you register for the Services, or after you become a user, we may ask for additional personal information, such as title, department name, fax number or additional company information, such as annual revenues, number of employees or industry. You can opt out of providing additional information by not entering it when asked. 

[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") does not distribute or share customer e-mail addresses, except as noted in its Terms of Service, or as may be required by law. 

[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") uses the information we collect to set up the Services for individuals and their organizations. We may also use the information to contact customers and prospects to further discuss their interest in our company, the Services we provide and ways we can improve them, and to send information such as announcements of promotions and events regarding our company or partners. We may also e-mail a customer newsletter and updates about the Services or the company. You can opt out of receiving these communications by replying to them at the time they are distributed or at any time by e-mailing [help@24hourwristbands.com](mailto:help@24hourwristbands.com). 

All financial and billing information that we collect through a NetBrands Web site and the Services is used solely to bill for the Services. NetBrands does not use this billing information for marketing or promotional purposes. Except as we explicitly state at the time we request information, or as provided for in the NetBrands Terms of Service, we do not disclose to any third party the information provided. 

[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") has integration relationships with third-party companies and individuals ("Integration Partners"). These relationships extend the functionality of the Services and the Integration Partner application or service ("Integrated Service") by allowing the Services and the Integrated Service to exchange customer data and to establish linked business processes between the two. Customers who pay [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") for use of the Services and use this Integrated Service are considered customers of both [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") and the Integration Partner. [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") and an Integration Partner may share customer contact, account, financial and billing information, and business data with respect to their integrated business relationship with the customer. The sharing of this information allows [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") and the Integration Partner to establish the identity of the shared customer and determine referral fees owed. This sharing also allows the Integration Partner to provide consolidated billing services to the shared customer and allows for the enhanced functionality of the integrated service. Shared contact, account, financial and billing information, and business data is governed by the NetBrands Terms of Service. 

[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing. This intermediary is solely a link in the distribution chain and is not permitted to store, retain, or use the information provided, except for the sole purpose of credit card processing. 

Other third parties, such as content providers, may provide information on a NetBrands Web site, but they are not permitted to collect any information, nor does [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") share any personally identifiable user information with these parties. 

[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") customers use [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") online applications to host data and information. [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") will not review, share, distribute, print, or reference any such data except as provided in the NetBrands Terms of Service, or as may be required by law. We will view or access individual records only with your permission (for example, to resolve a problem or support issue). Of course, users of the Services are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of their user registration and passwords. 

[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") may also collect certain information from visitors to a NetBrands Web site and customers of the Services, such as Internet addresses. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems and to administer the NetBrands Web site and Services in order to constantly improve quality. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from visitors and customers and provide such information to third parties.   

|  |   | 

## COOKIES

|    
---|---|---|---  
  
Cookies are files Web browsers place on a computer's hard drive. They are used to help us authenticate clients and provide timesaving shortcuts and preferences. [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") uses a persistent encrypted cookie, if the client requests, to save and retrieve individual authentication information as well as other per-client device preferences. When a visitor follows a link to the NetBrands Web site from an affiliate or promotion, [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") stores information about that affiliate or promotion in a session cookie. Acceptance of these cookies is optional. [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") issues a mandatory session cookie to each user of the Services only to record encrypted authentication information for the duration of a specific session. If you reject this cookie, access to and usage of the Services will be denied.   

|  |   | 

## THIRD PARTY SITES

|    
---|---|---|---  
  
The NetBrands Web site and online applications contain links to other Web sites. [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other Web sites. Customers and visitors must check the policy statement of these others Web sites to understand their policies. Customers and visitors who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information. It is your responsibility to keep such information private and confidential.   

|  |   | 

## SECURITY

|    
---|---|---|---  
  
[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") has security measures in place for the Services to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the data under NetBrands's control. When the Services are accessed using Netscape Navigator, or Microsoft Internet Explorer versions 4.0 or higher, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects information using both server authentication and data encryption to help ensure data is safe, secure and available only to you. [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") also implements an advanced security method based on dynamic data and encoded session identifications and hosts the Services in a secure server environment using a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. Finally, [**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") requires unique user names and passwords that must be entered each time a customer logs on. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of data.   

|  |   | 

## OPT-OUT POLICY

|    
---|---|---|---  
  
[**NetBrands**](http://www.netbrandscorp.com/ "NetBrandsCorp.Com") offers you a means to choose how we may use information you provided. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering the Services, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing information with third parties, send us a request specifying your new choice. Send your request to [help@24hourwristbands.com](mailto:help@24hourwristbands.com).   

|  |   | 

## CORRECTING AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

|    
---|---|---|---  
  
To update or change registration information, to update billing information, or to discontinue the Services, log on to the Services at a NetBrands Web site, click the Setup tab, and click links to these tasks. You can also correct and update information by e-mailing [help@24hourwristbands.com](mailto:help@24hourwristbands.com) or by calling 1-800-530-6218.   

|  |   | 

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

|    
---|---|---|---  
  
Questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the security practices of the Services should be directed to NetBrands's Security Administrator by e-mailing [help@24hourwristbands.com](mailto:help@24hourwristbands.com).
